

#### o Detalis o

Razipara , Mirpur 10

+8801849942053

M shakilfci461@gmail.com

o Links o

https://github.com/ShakilAhmmed

https://stackoverflow.com/cv/shakilahmmed https://www.hackerrank.com/shakilfci461

o Skills o

Python

django Diango

pHP

Laravel

Django Rest Framework

Javascript

Vue Js

MySQL

╚ JQuery , Ajax

Linux

# Reference

- Shariful Islam from Genex si.nayon@gmail.com
- Afroja Jainab , Feni Computer Institute 01711132353

#### △ Profile

Highly-dedicated, self-motivated, and enthusiastic Back-end Developer with more than 1+ years of experience in writing and executing code for web, analyzing user or business requirements as well as software testing, debugging and troubleshooting methods. Possess excellent communication, analytical, problem-solving, decision-making, time-management, team-working and multi-tasking skills.

## **Employment History**

Software Developer at SoftArch, Shyamoli, Dhaka

March 2020- present

- Developed Inventory Management Software
- Working on E-Commerce Application

Software Developer at TMSS ICT LTD, Mirpur, Dhaka

April 2019 - March 2020

- Developed Point Of Sale (POS) Application
- . Developed School Management Software
- Bug Fix On Microfinance Application

#### **Education**

Computer Science and Engineering, Bangladesh University Of Business and Technology, Rupnagar, Mirpur, Dhaka

June 2019 - Present

Diploma in Computer Science & Technology, Feni Computer Institute, Feni-3900 June 2015 - January 2019

CGPA: 3.52 / 4

Secondary School Certificate, Feni Central High School, Feni - 3900 January 2009 - February 2015

• GPA: 5.00 / 5 (Science)

#### □ COURSES

About Python and Django Framework, TMSS ICT LTD

February 2019 - April 2020

Python For Everybody, Coursera

July 2020 - July 2020

**Python Data Structures** 

August 2020 - August 2020

# **CONTRIBUTIONS**

- Hospital Management, https://hospitalerp.herokuapp.com/
- Pharma Sale Tracking, https://pharmacy-notify.herokuapp.com/
- BanglaWord, https://github.com/ShakilAhmmed/bangla-word